{
    "subject": "resource/Jesus_of_Montreal",
    "predicate": "property/director",
    "object": "resource/Denys_Arcand",
    "human_readable": "Denys Arcand directed Jesus of Montreal.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8833900094032288,
            "question": "Who directed the film Jesus of Montreal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7083126902580261,
            "question": "What is Denys Arcand known for directing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6933867931365967,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Denys Arcand?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6451728343963623,
            "question": "Where was Jesus of Montreal filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.57040935754776,
            "question": "What year was Jesus of Montreal released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5582754015922546,
            "question": "What themes might be explored in a film titled Jesus of Montreal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5196952223777771,
            "question": "Who are some famous actors who may have starred in Jesus of Montreal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44212499260902405,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Denys Arcand that you know of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39297810196876526,
            "question": "What genre is Jesus of Montreal likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.370361328125,
            "question": "What are some critical reviews of Jesus of Montreal?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Denys Arcand directed Jesus of Montreal.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1026_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Jesus of Montreal likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1026_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other films directed by Denys Arcand that you know of?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1026_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some famous actors who may have starred in Jesus of Montreal?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1026_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1026_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1026_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1026_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1026_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1026_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1026_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1026_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1026_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1026_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1026_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Denys Arcand directed the film \"Jesus of Montreal,\" making the statement correct."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}